gtefcu.org 2016-04-01

# FACTS

                                                                                                                Rev 12/2014
                     WHAT DOES GTE Federal Credit Union DBA GTE FINANCIAL
FACTS                DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                 Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                     consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                     how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                     understand what we do.
What?                The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                     have with us. This information can include:
                            Social Security number and Transaction History
                            Account Balances        and Account Transactions
                            Credit History          and Mortgage Rates and Payments
How?                 All financial companies need to share members' personal information to run their everyday
                     business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                     members' personal information; the reasons GTE Financial chooses to share; and whether
                     you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information                       Does GTE share?             Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain
your account(s), respond to court orders and legal                          Yes                               No
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes—
to offer our products and services to you                                   Yes                              Yes*
For joint marketing with other ﬁnancial companies                           Yes                              Yes*
For our afﬁliates’ everyday business purposes—
information about your transactions and experiences                         Yes                              Yes*
For our afﬁliates’ everyday business purposes—
information about your creditworthiness                                      No                        We don't share
For nonafﬁliates to market to you                                            No                        We don't share
To limit               Call 813.871.2690 or 888.871.2690 ext.40401
our sharing           Please note:
                      IfIf you
                           you are    new member we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this
                               are aa new
                      notice.
                      * You may contact us at any time to limit our sharing of printed and electronic marketing materials
                      tailored specifically for you.
Questions?            Call 813.871.2690 or 888.871.2690

  Page 2
   Who we are
                                       GTE Financial
   Who is providing this notice?
   What we do
   How does GTE Financial             To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
   protect my personal information?   and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                      These measures include computer safeguards and secured ﬁles
                                      and buildings.
   How does GTE Financial             We collect your personal information, for example, when you
   collect my personal information?
                                           Open An Account              or Show Your Driver's License
                                           Apply for a Loan             or Make a Wire Transfer
                                          Give us Your Employment History
                                       We also collect your personal information from others, such as, credit
                                       bureaus, and other companies.
   Why can’t I limit all sharing?     Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                          sharing for afﬁliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                           about your creditworthiness
                                          afﬁliates from using your information to market to you
                                          sharing for nonafﬁliates to market to you
                                      State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                      limit sharing.
   What happens when I limit sharing
                                       Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
   for an account I hold jointly with
   someone else?
   Deﬁnitions
   Afﬁliates                          Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                      ﬁnancial and nonﬁnancial companies.
                                           Our affiliates include companies with a GTE Financial name.
   Nonafﬁliates                       Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                      ﬁnancial and nonﬁnancial companies.
                                           GTE Financial does not share with nonaffiliates so they
                                            can market to you.
   Joint marketing                    A formal agreement between nonafﬁliated ﬁnancial companies that
                                      together market ﬁnancial products or services to you.
                                           Our joint marketing partners include investment, insurance and
                                            other financial services companies.
DISC7 12/14
